canadaeast.com 2007-10-08

# CanadaEast Online

**Last Updated** : July 17, 2007

Welcome to our site. CanadaEast Interactive has created this Privacy Policy in order to document and communicate our commitment to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls.

Our Privacy Policy is designed to give you, the user, more information on how information is collected, used and disclosed through this site. This document, together with our Terms of Use and Copyright Information govern our affiliates, partners, advertisers and CanadaEast Interactive's relationship with you in relation to this website. Please read them carefully.

The term "CanadaEast" or "us" or "we" refers to the owner of the web site, CanadaEast Interactive, whose registered office is 939 Main Street, Moncton, New Brunswick E1C 8P3.

The term "CE Network" refers collectively to sites owned by or managed by CanadaEast Interactive. The term "you" refers to the user or viewer of our website or any persons with accessibility to this web site.

## A. Defining Personal Information

CE Network is committed to providing our web site visitors with the advantages of online technology. Part of this commitment may include providing an interactive and personalized experience. CE Network may collect information including your name, email address, civic and postal address, telephone number, recorded communications, subscription information, product preferences, related billing records and other user supplied demographic data (hereinafter referred to as "Personally Identifiable Information") subjected to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

Please note this policy applies only to information collected by CE Network online and does not impact information collected or used by CE Network or its affiliates through other means.

## B. Information Collection

CE Network will only ask for information about you that we need and will only ask for it when we need it. When we ask you for the information, we will explain to you why we need it and what we are going to do with it.

We will seek your prior consent to the collection, use and disclosure of the information as required by applicable privacy legislation. Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you can refuse to consent to our collection, use or disclosure of information about you. You may also withdraw your consent to any further collection, use or disclosure of information about you at any time by giving us reasonable notice. Please note that some features and functions of this site that require personal information may become unavailable should you withdrawl consent. If our intended disclosures or uses of information change, we will notify you accordingly on this policy page.

CE Network collects and stores various information depending on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. CE Network collects and uses your personal information primarily for the purpose of providing you with the products and services you have requested from us, including daily delivery of news, premium access and related content.

You may visit many pages on our site without providing any Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information is collected by the CE Network only when you specifically and knowingly choose to provide it to us. 

You may optionally choose to provide information, such as when you register for access to portions of our site, subscribe to premium services, request certain features (e.g., newsletters, news updates and other products), sign up for a newspaper subscription or make a purchase. You may also choose to provide Personally Identifiable Information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities, comments, discussions, message boards and chat rooms and other interactive areas of our site.

Like most web sites, CE Network also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. As an example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use "cookie" technology. This information can not be used to identify you and is referred to as "Aggregated Information".

Information that has been disclosed CE Network as provided by another user, for example email addresses utilized when using out shared feature, are not collected or stored by CE Network. CE Network does not maintain databases of these email addresses. If you wish to not receive share email notices from CE Network visitors, you may be blocked by contacting CE Network.

## C. Use of Your Information

We will use your information only as permitted by law. Aggregated Information may be used in many ways. As one example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.

Collected Personally Identifiable Information may be used to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on CE Network to communicate with you regarding your account, subscription and premium services, our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, products and services offered by CE Network and other CanadaEast affiliates, advertisers and partners, administration of sweepstakes and contests, processing e-commerce transactions and execution of other site operations included in our services or requested by you. We reserve the right to share this information with other CanadaEast Interactive business units and affiliates, including for example our affiliated newspapers and entities in which CanadaEast has an ownership interest.

Unless you specifically authorize us to release your personal information, or release is required or permitted by law, the CE Network will not sell, lease, trade or otherwise permit access to your personal information to other third parties.

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

Your personal information will not be used for any other purpose than those permitted in this Privacy Policy without your consent.

## D. Advertisers & Affiliates

CE Network expects its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a CE Network page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through CE Network you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. CE Network is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising may be served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. CE Network does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

A cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the "Cookies" folder on your hard drive after you close your browser, and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the CE Network or other sites. We use persistent and session cookies to analyze and enhance your experience on the CE Network, and we may use third party ad technology to serve ads. The data that is collected is the property of CE Network, not the third party. We also may allow third parties called ad networks or ad servers to serve ads to you on CE Network. Cookies enable them to compile information about where you, or others who have used your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information makes it possible for the ad technology, ad servers and ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements to you on CE Network. CE Network does not have access to the cookies that may be placed on your computer by third-party ad technology, ad servers or ad networks. Those parties that use cookies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our site, such as in message boards, chat areas or in advertising or notices you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of CE Network and this policy.

## E. Security

CE Network is committed to protecting your privacy. Security measures, such as locked cabinets, change control procedures, restricted access and the use of passwords and encryption have been adopted to protect your personal information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Our employees have been trained to respect your privacy at all times and those employees with access to your personal information shall use your personal information strictly in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business.

## F. Avoiding Fraud

CE Network and our affiliates, partners and partners will never solicit you by email, telephone or means and request that you log in to the site to update personal information, confirm a purchase or otherwise confirm or disclose Personally Identifiable Information. 

Go directly to our website by typing it into your web browser or using a bookmark before logging in. Never click on a link in an email that takes you to a CE Network log in page. CE Network will never send you an email with a direct log in link.

If you believe that you are being targeted by a fraudulent communication, please contact us immediately so that we may investigate. If you have been the victim of a fraudulent communication and have mistakenly provided a userID or password that may allow persons to exploit your Personally Identifiable Information, contact us immediately so that we may disable access.

## G. Access & Accuracy

If you have any questions about the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by CE Network, or if you simply want to know whether we have any of your personal information on file, you may contact CanadaEast. 

Except in limited circumstances, as specifically provided by applicable privacy legislation, the CE Network can tell you whether they hold personal information about you. 

CE Network attempts to ensure that information about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. In the event you have questions about the accuracy of factual information we have collected about you, CE Network will provide the means to correct it or if unavailable update it upon request. If we have disclosed inaccurate information about you to a third party, we will be pleased to contact the third party in order to correct the information.

CE Network will only refuse access to information about you in those circumstances permitted or required by applicable privacy legislation. If a CanWest Company refuses access to you, it will provide you with the reasons for its refusal upon request. Exceptions may include information that contains references to other individuals, information that cannot be disclosed for legal, security or commercial proprietary reasons, and information that is subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilege. CE Network will respond to your requests for access in accordance with applicable privacy legislation.

## H. Children

CE Network does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children. If we discover we have received any information from a child in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe CE Network has any information from or containing a child's Personally Identifiable Information, please contact us. CE Network does not maintain databases about children.

## I. Conclusion

CE Network reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

This policy and the use of this site are governed by the laws of New Brunswick and Canada. Any claim related to the site or this policy shall be brought in a federal or provincial court in Moncton, New Brunswick within one year after the claim arises. You agree no such claim may be brought as a class action. Users of CE Network consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy. CE Network is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Canada. If you are located outside Canada, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to Canada. You hereby consent to this transfer.

## J. Inquiries

You may need to disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to contact CE Network so that we may reply to your request.

If you have any questions, comments, concerns or requests regarding this policy you may write to CanadaEast Interactive for more information at:

**CanadaEast Interactive**

939 Main Street

Moncton, New Brunswick E1C 8P3

Canada
